(This machine's IP is 192.168.33.133. The User of this machine is Administrator. The hostname is RYAN2C2-WIN. The powershell version is @{Version=5.1.19041.1151}.  Todays date is 09/09/2021 16:09:33)
(This machine's IP is 192.168.33.133. The User of this machine is Administrator. The hostname is RYAN2C2-WIN. The powershell version is @{Version=5.1.19041.1151}.  Todays date is 09/09/2021 16:10:08)
(This machine's IP is 192.168.33.133. The User of this machine is Administrator. The hostname is RYAN2C2-WIN. The powershell version is @{Version=5.1.19041.1151}.  Todays date is 09/09/2021 16:10:42)
